donquijote.org 2016-11-22

# Privacy Policy | don Quijote

Our most popular **Spanish courses**

Home » Why don Quijote? » **Privacy Policy**

  * ### Learn Spanish

  * Why Study Spanish?
    1. Included services
    2. dQ guarantees
    3. Students opinions
    4. Recognitions
    5. Instituto Cervantes Scholarships
    6. Academic Credits
  * Accommodation
  * Video & Photo Galleries
  * Monthly Newsletters

We Value Your Privacy  
What Information Does donQuijote.org Collect?  
How Secure Is My Personal Information?  
How Does donQuijote.org Use My Personal Information?  
How Can I Access or Change My Personal Information?  
About Changes To This Policy  
How to Contact Us

* * *

**We Value Your Privacy**  
donQuijote.org knows that you care how your personal information is used and protected, and we appreciate your trust that we will do so responsibly. We take the protection of your information seriously. This policy describes our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used.

Please read this policy carefully because by visiting or using the don Quijote Web site you give your consent that your data may be processed according to this Privacy Policy.

* * *

**What Information Does donQuijote.org Collect?**  
We collect information from you to help us personalize and improve your don Quijote experience, to process your online requests, and to send you communications to which you have subscribed.

 **INFORMATION YOU ENTER IN FORMS**

  * On certain pages, you have the ability to order products, make requests, and register to receive various materials. The types of personal information collected on these pages are: first name, last name, e-mail address, phone, mailing address, information about your level and motivation for studying Spanish, and credit/debit card information (only when you purchase an item, such as an online Spanish course).
  * You can always choose not to submit the information requested, understanding that you may be unable to take advantage of some features.
  * On certain pages, you can submit basic information about other individuals. For example, if you want to send a link to a friend about our services, you will need to submit your friend’s e-mail address.
  * All of your personal data will be used only for purpose for which you submit them. For example, your friend’s e-mail will only be used to forward him your e-mail recommendation.

**INFORMATION COLLECTED ELECTRONICALLY**

  * We also store certain types of electronic information when you interact with us on our Web site.
  * We use "cookies" and obtain certain information from your Web browser. By transferring these alphanumeric identifiers to your computer's hard drive, we are able to recognize you during future visits to our Web site, so that you can benefit from special features, such as Auto Logon. You can disable your computer from accepting new cookies if you choose, understanding that you will then be unable to take full advantage of some of our Web site features.
  * We also use Web metrics tools to automatically track certain electronic information about your visits to our Web site. We use this aggregate information to do internal research on our visitors’ interests and behaviour, to help us better understand and serve them. This information includes the URL that you just came from, which URL you go to next, what browser you are using, and your IP address. We use this aggregate data without connecting it with any personally identifying information.

* * *

**How Secure is My Personal Information?**

  * To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use and transmission of your information, we have implemented the appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information that we collect from you online.
  * To protect your information, we use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts all of the information that you input into our forms and the information you provide when performing a credit card transaction. We also encrypt your password whenever you log on to your don Quijote account.
  * Concerning credit card transactions, we only reveal the last five digits of your credit card numbers when confirming an order with you. Of course, we transmit the entire credit card number to the appropriate credit card company during order processing.

* * *

**How Will donQuijote.org Use My Information?**

  * We use the information that we collect from you to process your requests, enhance and personalize your don Quijote experience, and, only when you have given us permission to do so, to send you newsletters and other e-mail communications.
  * We use aggregate and non-personally identifying information (such as the URL from which you arrive at our site) without using any information that would identify you. For instance, we will use this non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our Web site and to track results of marketing and promotional campaigns.
  * We never use or share the personally identifiable information you provide to us online in ways unrelated to the those described in this policy, nor will we share your information with third parties without your permission. Your data will only be accessible to and used by the don Quijote group of businesses, and only for the purpose for which you submitted them. Full list of don Quijote entities with access to your data. 
    * DON QUIJOTE SALAMANCA S.L. (B-37263621)
    * DON QUIJOTE GRANADA S.L. (B-18329615)
    * DON QUIJOTE EUROLINGUA S.L. (B-37263639)
    * DON QUIJOTE MADRID S.L. (B-37367935)
    * DON QUIJOTE TENERIFE S.L. (B-38593091)
    * DON QUIJOTE SEVILLA S.L. (B-37370962)
    * DON QUIJOTE VALENCIA S.L. (B-37390614)
    * DON QUIJOTE PUERTO DE LA CRUZ S.L. (B-38566170)
    * DON QUIJOTE SERVICIOS AUXILIARES A.I.E.  (G-37412681)
    * R.F.C. DON QUIJOTE GUANAJUATO
  * Your personal data will be used only for the purposes for which you submit them. For example, if you submit a friend’s e-mail to our “Tell a Friend” feature, his e-mail will only be used to forward your e-mail recommendation.
  * Please be aware that when you click on an advertising banner on our Web site that takes you to a different Web site, you begin to interact according to the privacy policy of the other Web site. We encourage you to read the posted privacy statement of any Web site you visit before providing your personal information.

* * *

**How Can I Access or Change My Personal Information?**

  * **All Visitors:** You have the right to request a copy of the personal information don Quijote holds about you, to make any changes, and to ask that it be deleted. Please address requests to the addresses listed below, in the section How to Contact Us
  * **dQ Members:** If you are a don Quijote member, you can access all of your personally identifying information by logging onto your account and selecting Edit My Profile in the Members menu. To protect your privacy and security, we take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. You can also edit your Members opt-in choices through the Control Panel in the same Members menu.
  * You may request deletion of your don Quijote Member account by contacting Members Support. Please note that some information may possibly remain in our archived records after your account has been deleted.

* * *

**About Changes to This Privacy Policy**  
This privacy policy was last modified on December 9,2005. Don Quijote may revise this policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes, we will post those amendments on our Web site so that you are always aware of the information we collect, how we use it and how you can access or update your personal information.

* * *

**How to Contact Us**  
DON QUIJOTE SALAMANCA, S.L. UNIPERSONAL (B-37263621)  
Placentinos 2 - 37008 – Salamanca, España  
Tel: +34 923 268860 Fax: +34 923 260651  
Inscrita en el Registro Mercantil, Folio 49 del Libro 72 de Sociedades,  
inscripción 10ª de la Hoja número SA 2235

* * *
